Mykola Avramuk

Personal information

Date of birth: 16.12.1995

Home: Ukraine Location: Spain

Email: avramuk89@gmail.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/avramukk
Github: github.com/avramukk

Website: avramukk.com

Summary of Qualifications

4 years in software development

5 years in System Administration of TV channel infrastructure

Expertise

Test planning and strategy development

Functional and non-functional testing

Bash, Python

Playwright, Cypress, Postman

AWS: EC2, ECS, S3, Lambda, Route53, Api Gateway, CloudFormation, CodeBuild, CodePipeline

Terraform, Docker, Kubernetes, Ansible

Github Actions, Gitlab CI

Linux, Windows, macOS, Android, iOS

GStreamer, FFmpeg, vMix, LiveU, AWS Elemental Live

Github Projects, TestRail, Trello, Bitbucket SDI and IP video transport, Oasys System

MPEG (2,4,HEVC) Video, SRT, Zixi, RTMP, HLS, WebRTC, NDI

Languages

English - intermediate Ukrainian – native

Experience

DevOps Engineer

Serverless Graphics, Contract

Oct 2023 – Feb 2024

Responsibility: IaC for serverless service for generating Ad video graphics and insertion into streams

Technology: CloudFormation, Lambda, ECS, Fargate, Docker, Bash, Python, Ffmpeg, HLS

DevOps Engineer

Cyber Regiment, Volunteer

Sep 2022 – Present

Responsibility: IaC for NEST.JS application with GitlabCI

Technology: Nest, Typescript, Bash, Gitlab CI

QA Engineer

Mixa.live, Contract Mar 2022 – Present

QA: Full QA process of SDLC for the cloud video switcher

DevOps: Fully migration to another AWS account.

Technology: Live Video Streaming, Linux, Web, SRT, RTMP, Zixi, Terraform

QA Engineer & Project Manager

VVCR, Contract

Jul 2020 – Present

Responsibility: Full QA process from scratch of cloud-based virtual video control room system (VVCR). Managing SDLC in the team of 4 people

Technology: Scrum, Test Planning, System Testing, Regression Testing, Live Video Streaming, API Testing, Manual Testing, Test Automation

QA Engineer

RIVET, Contract

Jul 2020 - Present

Responsibility:

Full QA process from scratch of Broadcast Tools (Windows, macOS, iOS, Android) and Platform (web) for Remote Streaming via SRT Protocols.

Technology: Test Planning, System Testing, Regression Testing, Live Video Streaming, API Testing, Manual Testing, Test Automation

Video Streaming Engineer

1+1 MEDIA, Shift-time

Aug 2018 - Jul 2020

Responsibility: Live video streaming, Installation and support of devices and applications for

broadcasts

Technology: AWS Elemental Live, LiveU Central, vMix, OBS, FFmpeg, RTMP, HLS, UDP

Broadcasting Automation Engineer

TV channel, Shift-time

Mar 2020 - Jun 2021

Responsibility: Servers Administering for Video Content Delivery pipeline for post production

Technology: Windows Server, Linux, MacOS, Avid Technology Products

IT Support Engineer

TV channel, Shift-time

Feb 2018 - May 2020

Responsibility: Technical Support

Technology: Windows, MacOS, Linux, Avid Technology Products

Broadcast Specialist

TV channel, Shift-time

Sep 2016 - Feb 2018

Responsibility: Broadcast quality control, planning of the broadcast grid, quick response to any

problems in the final broadcast signal

Technology: Oasys Air System, Broadcasting, Television

Educational background

National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic Institute" Master's degree, Intellectual technologies of microsystem radio-electronic equipment Sep 2017 - Sep 2018

National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic Institute" Bachelor's degree, Telecommunications and radio engineering Sep 2013 - Aug 2017